iloggo.com 2009-08-22

# iloggo

### Privacy Policy

This document is a regulation on privacy protection and a declaration of respecting by iloggo.pl these users? rights which result from the Act on Personal Data Protection. Our concern is expressed by:

  1. complying strictly with valid laws and regulations, including: 
    * The Act of 29.08.97. on Personal Data Protection (Journal of Law No.133 item 883 with changes);
    * The Decree by the Minister of the Internal Affairs and Administration of 29.04.2004 on the documentation of personal data processing as well as technical and organizational conditions that should be followed by information equipment and systems used to personal data processing (Journal of Law of May 1, 2004). 
  2. collecting and processing only those data to collecting and processing of which the user has given his or her consent.
  3. providing a possibility of access and making changes in personal data for each user of iloggo.pl
  4. making every effort to prevent any third parties from access to personal data bases that are in possession of iloggo.pl 
  5. not providing any third parties and entities with personal data without the user?s consent
  6. making explanations about any questions and remarks connected with privacy policy.

By registering in iloggo.pl, the user confirms his or her acceptance of the regulations included in Privacy Policy.

## Users under 18 years old

In the registration process iloggo.pl does not demand that users should give data enabling iloggo.pl to determine their age. The e-mail address given during the registration will be used only to send information about the functioning of the service. In case of underage users, their parents or legal guardians should give their consent to make the e-mail address available.

## The scope of collected and processed data

iloggo reduces the collecting and processing of information about users to the absolute minimum, which can enable the provision of services of the highest standard. Data used by iloggo.pl come from a form filled in by users during the registration, cookies stored in the user?s computer while he or she is using iloggo.pl service, IP number stored in access logins of the iloggo.pl servers and any correspondence coming to iloggo.pl e-mail addresses.

## Making changes in Privacy Policy

iloggo reserves the right to make changes in the aforementioned Privacy Policy. The changes come into force on the day of their publication. Using the iloggo.pl service after this date will mean the acceptance of the new rules. On the user?s request, iloggo.pl makes any information about changes available.
